techjockey.com 2019-04-16

# Privacy Policy | Privacy & Terms | Techjockey

We value the trust you place in us. Thatâ€™s why we insist upon the highest standards for secure transactions and customer information privacy. Please read the following statement to learn about our information gathering and dissemination practices. 

### Please Note:

Our privacy policy is subject to change at any time without prior notice. To make sure you are up-to-date with respect to any changes, please review this policy periodically. 

By visiting this Website, you agree to be bound by the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree, please do not use or access our Website. 

By mere use of the Website, you expressly consent to our use and disclosure of your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and subject to the Terms of Use. 

### 1\. Collection of Personally Identifiable Information and other Information

When you use our Website, we collect and store your personal information which is provided by you from time to time. Our primary purpose in doing so is to provide you a safe, efficient, smooth and customized experience. This allows us to provide services and features that most likely meet your needs, and to customize our Website to make your experience safer and easier. More importantly, while doing so we collect personal information from you that we consider necessary for achieving this purpose. 

In general, you can browse the Website without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself. Once you give us your personal information, you are not anonymous to us. Where possible, we indicate which fields are required and which fields are optional. You always have the option to not provide information by choosing not to use a particular service or feature on the Website. We may automatically track certain information about you based upon your behaviour on our Website. We use this information to do internal research on our user's demographics, interests, and behaviour to better understand, protect and serve our users. This information is compiled and analyzed on an aggregated basis. This information may include the URL that you just came from (whether this URL is on our Website or not), which URL you next go to (whether this URL is on our Website or not), your computer browser information, and your IP address. 

We use data collection devices such as "cookies" on certain pages of the Website to help analyse our web page flow, measure promotional effectiveness, and promote trust and safety. "Cookies" are small files placed on your hard drive that assist us in providing our services. We offer certain features that are only available when a "cookie" is used. 

We also use cookies to allow you to enter your password less frequently during a session. Cookies can also help us provide information that is targeted to your interests. Most cookies are "session cookies," meaning that they are automatically deleted from your hard drive at the end of a session. You are always free to decline our cookies if your browser permits, although in that case you may not be able to use certain features on the Website and you may be required to re-enter your password more frequently during a session.

Additionally, you may encounter "cookies" or other similar devices on certain pages of the Website that are placed by third parties. We do not control the use of cookies by third parties. 

If you choose to post messages on our message boards or leave feedback, we will collect that information and retain it as necessary to resolve disputes, provide customer support and troubleshoot problems as permitted by law. 

If you send us personal correspondence, such as emails or letters, or if other users or third parties send us correspondence about your activities or postings on the Website, we may collect such information into a file specific to you. 

### 2\. Use of Demographic / Profile Data / Your Information

We use personal information to provide the services you request. We will provide you the ability to opt-out of using your personal information to market to you. We use your personal information to resolve disputes; troubleshoot problems; help promote a safe service; collect money; measure consumer interest in our products and services, inform you about online and offline offers, products, services, and updates; customize your experience; detect and protect us against error, fraud and other criminal activity; enforce our terms and conditions; and as otherwise described to you at the time of collection.

In our efforts to continually improve our product and service offerings, we collect and analyze demographic and profile data about our usersâ€™ activity on our Website.

We identify and use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Website. Your IP address is also used to help identify you and to gather broad demographic information.

We will occasionally ask you to complete optional online surveys. These surveys may ask you for contact information and demographic information (like pin code, age, or income level). 

### Cookies

A "cookie" refers to a small piece of information sent from a website which is stored by a web server on a web browser while the user is browsing. We place both permanent and temporary cookies in your computer's hard drive. The cookies do not contain any of your personally identifiable information

### 3\. Sharing of personal information

We may share your personal information with our other corporate entities and affiliates. These entities and affiliates may market to you unless you explicitly state otherwise. 

We may disclose personal information to third parties. This disclosure may be required for us to provide you access to our Services, to comply with our legal obligations, to facilitate our marketing and advertising activities, or to prevent, detect, quell, and investigate fraudulent or illegal activities related to our Services. We do not divulge your personal information to third parties for their marketing and advertising purposes without your explicit consent. 

We may disclose personal information if required to do so by law or in good faith that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to respond to subpoenas, court orders, or other legal process. We may divulge personal information to law enforcement offices, third party rights owners, or others in the good faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to " enforce our Terms or Privacy Policy; respond to claims that an advertisement, posting or other content violates the rights of a third party; or protect the rights, property or personal safety of our users or the public. 

We and our affiliates will share/sell some or all your personal information with/to another business entity should we (or our assets) plan to merge with, or be acquired by that business entity, or re-organization, amalgamation, restructuring of business. Should such a transaction occur that other business entity (or the new combined entity) will be required to follow this privacy policy with respect to your personal information. 

### 4\. Links to Other Sites

Our Website links to other websites that may collect personally identifiable information about you. Techjockey is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of those linked websites. 

### 5\. Security Precautions

Our Website has stringent security measures to help us protect the loss, misuse, and modification of the information under our control. Whenever you change your account information or access your account, we offer the use of a secure server. After procuring your information, we adhere to strict security guidelines, protecting it against unauthorized access and misuse. 

### 6\. Choice/Opt-Out

We provide all users with the opportunity to opt-out of receiving non-essential (promotional, marketing-related) communications from us on behalf of our partners, and from us in general, after setting up an account. If you want to remove your contact information from all Techjockey.com lists and newsletters, please visit Techjockey.
